{
    "subject": "Iain_Softley",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Backbeat__film_",
    "human_readable": "Iain Softley created the film Backbeat.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8101701140403748,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Iain Softley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7072010636329651,
            "question": "Who directed the film Backbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5088402032852173,
            "question": "What is the plot of Backbeat about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4298449456691742,
            "question": "What year was Backbeat released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4044162929058075,
            "question": "Can you name other films directed by Iain Softley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40367501974105835,
            "question": "What might be a theme explored in Backbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3613373935222626,
            "question": "What genre is Backbeat likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3551078140735626,
            "question": "Who are some potential actors that could have been in Backbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3546425998210907,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did Backbeat receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2592121660709381,
            "question": "Where might you be able to watch Backbeat?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Iain Softley created the film Backbeat.",
            "html": "yago_5999_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards or recognition did Backbeat receive?",
            "html": "yago_5999_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some potential actors that could have been in Backbeat?",
            "html": "yago_5999_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Backbeat likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_5999_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5999_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n* There are multiple documents mentioning Iain Softley and his work on various films, including Backbeat.\n* In one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5999/re-ranker-msmarco/138.txt), it is explicitly stated that \"His films include Backbeat...\". This suggests that Iain Softley was involved in creating the film Backbeat.\n* Additionally, another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5999/re-ranker-msmarco/138.txt) mentions that \"Softley first wrote and directed a biopic on Stuart Sutcliffe, which became the film Backbeat\".\n* Another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5999/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt) mentions that Softley \"came upon photographs of ex-Beatle Stuart Sutcliffe... and started looking for a rites-of-passage story to make into a feature film\" which became Backbeat.\n\nGiven this information, it is clear that Iain Softley was indeed involved in creating the film Backbeat. Therefore:\n\n{ \"output\": \"yes\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly mention that Iain Softley directed and wrote the film \"Backbeat,\" which supports the statement that Iain Softley created the film \"Backbeat.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}